Kate Braid fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Kate Braid fonds
1963-2013
F-10
Q100144597
9.08 m of textual records 180 sound recordings; includes original and access copies 3 moving images; includes original videocassettes and digitized access copies 1 photograph
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Braid, Kate
Kate Braid is a Vancouver poet, carpenter, trade unionist and educator. Born in Calgary, Alberta and raised in Montreal, Que, Braid received a Bachelor of Arts degree in English and history from Mount Allison University in 1967.
In 1979 she earned her Master of Arts degree in the Communications Department at Simon Fraser University with a thesis entitled Invisible Women: Women in Non-Traditional Occupations in B.C. Meanwhile, she had begun working in the construction industry herself, and in 1983 received her Interprovincial Trades Qualification and Apprenticeship Certificate (Red Seal) for carpentry construction from the Pacific Vocational Institute (later renamed the British Columbia Institute of Technology or BCIT). She was the first woman member of the Vancouver local of the International Carpenters' Union (Local 452, later 1995). In 1997 she earned her Master of Fine Arts in Creative Writing at the University of British Columbia.
She continued to work in trades until 1989, forming her own company, Sisters Construction (1983-1987). Kate Braid was a founding member of the Vancouver Women in Trades Association, an advocacy and support organization that existed from 1979 to 1987.
Braid has written extensively on women and trades, including two booklets profiling Canadian tradeswomen for the Women's Bureau of Labour Canada. In addition, she prepared radio documentaries for the CBC's Ideas radio program. She has taught numerous courses and workshops since 1980, and in 1989 became the first full-time woman instructor in construction carpentry at BCIT. From 1991 to 1995, as Director of Labour Programs at SFU, she served as a liaison between academia and labour. Braid has also taught creative writing at Malaspina College (now Vancouver Island University), SFU and UBC.
Her poems and other writings have appeared in many journals and anthologies, and have been broadcast on radio and television. Her first collection of her poetry, Covering Rough Ground, won the Pat Lowther Memorial Prize in 1991. Her next collection, To this Cedar Fountain, was shortlisted for the Dorothy Livesay Poetry Prize in 1995. Her other publications include: Red Bait: Struggles of a Mine Local (1998), Inward to the Bones: Georgia O'Keeffe's Journey with Emily Carr (1998), Emily Carr: Rebel Artist (2000), In Fine Form: The Canadian Book of Form Poetry (2005), A Well-Mannered Storm: the Glenn Gould poems (2008), Turning Left to the Ladies (2009), and her prose memoir "Journeywoman: Swinging a Hammer in a Man's World" (2012).
She and her partner live in Vancouver, BC.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
Fonds consists of records relating to Braid's life and work as a student, teacher, carpenter, and writer.
The first five series from Braid's first donation in 1995 are comprised primarily of interview material relating to Canadian women in trades, in the form of sound recordings, transcripts, notes, and drafts of profiles generated by Kate Braid in the course of four projects: her Master's thesis (1978-1979); a convention in Holland and subsequent trip to Denmark (1984); the Labour Canada booklets (1988); and the CBC Ideas program (1990). Also includes some correspondence, logbooks and published reference material.
The next series from several additional accruals in 2009 to 2013 consist of records arising from many aspects of Braid's life. These records include drafts and notes from Braid's writing, projects for CBC Ideas, women in trades, her company, Sisters Construction, and other writing and teaching projects.
There is also a large series of correspondence, including letters and emails (printed out) between Braid and other writers, her family, and business correspondents. Finally, there is a series of Braid's diaries, which she has kept regularly from the 1960s to 2012.
The fonds is arranged in 24 series:
1. Master's thesis interviews
2. Europe interviews
3. Labour Canada interviews
4. CBC interviews
5. Women in trade
6. In Fine Form: the Canadian Book of Form Poetry
7. Red Bait: Struggles of a Mine Local
8. A Well-mannered Storm: the Glenn Gould Poems
9. Emily Carr: Rebel Artist
10. Inward to the Bones: Georgia Okeeffe's Journey with Emily Carr
11. Vancouver Island Highway Project Road to Equity
12. CBC Ideas: Men of the Deep
13. Appointment calendars
14. Correspondence
15. Personal and early accomplishments
16. Writing and teaching projects
17. Turning Left to the Ladies
18. Journeywoman
19. Diaries
20. First drafts and handwritten notes
21. Sisters construction
22. Publications
23. Covering Rough Ground
24. To this Cedar Fountain
Sound recordings; Textual records; Photographic materials; Women; Labour; Arts and culture
The records were donated to the Archives by Kate Braid in 1996 with subsequent accruals in 2009, 2010, and 2014.
All accruals have been processed as of March 2015.
See also the records of the Vancouver Women in Trades Association (fonds F-9), of which Kate Braid was a founding member.
Access to the interviews, transcripts, notes and drafts of profiles relating to individuals is provided through a research agreement. Consult the archivist for further details.
Access to the F-10-14-3 Personal correspondence and F-10-19 Diaries series are restricted in whole until December 31, 2015. Permission must be sought by the donor for in order to access these series.
Some files or items may contain personal or confidential information. Files or items marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release and, as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file and item lists and consult the reference archivist for more details.
- Master's thesis interviews, 1978 - 1979; F-10-1; 22 cm of textual records 23 sound recordings 89 .wav files; Physical description: series contains 23 interviews stored on 72 audio cassettes, including originals and access copies. Access copies do not currently exist for all sound recordings. 53 of the 72 audio cassettes have been digitized to .wav format.
  published
  Series consists of documents relating to interviews with tradeswomen and others conducted by Kate Braid throughout British Columbia in the course of research for her Master of Arts thesis at Simon Fraser University. Series includes audio cassettes, transcripts, notes, and correspondence.
  - Broswick, Pat audio recording, transcript and notes, 1978-1979; F-10-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Broswick, Pat; Textual records; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Restricted in whole
    - Broswick, Pat [audio], September 1978 - March 1979; F-10-1-0-0-1-1; 2 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2888, Audio cassette OBJ-2889)
      Broswick, Pat; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2888 and OBJ-2889 also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C10-1-0-1.1, C10-1-0-1.2, F-10-item2, F-10-item3, F-10-1-0-0-0-1.
      - Obj-2888_sideA.wav
      - Obj-2888_sideB.wav
      - Obj-2889_sideA.wav
      - Obj-2889_sideB.wav
  - Croquette, Charlotte audio recording, transcript and notes, [ca 1978]; F-10-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Croquette, Charlotte; Textual records; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    - Croquette, Charlotte and Linda Bernard [audio], 5 October 1978; F-10-1-0-0-2-1; 2 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2890, Audio cassette OBJ-2891)
      Croquette, Charlotte; Linda Bernard; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2890 and OBJ-2891 also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C10-1-0-2.1, C10-1-0-2.2, F-10-item32, F-10-item33, F-10-1-0-0-0-2.
      - Obj-2890_side1.wav
      - Obj-2890_side2.wav
      - Obj-2891_side1.wav
      - Obj-2891_side2.wav
  - Doll, Judy audio recording and transcript, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Doll, Judy; Textual records; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    - Doll, Judy [audio], 24 July 1978; F-10-1-0-0-3-1; 2 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2892, Audio cassette OBJ-2893)
      Doll, Judy; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2892 and OBJ-2893 also available in .wmp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C10-1-0-3.1, C10-1-0-3.2, F-10-item48, F-10-item49, F-10-1-0-0-0-3.
      - Obj-2892_sideA.wav
      - Obj-2892_sideB.wav
      - Obj-2893_sideA.wav
      - Obj-2893_sideB.wav
  - Dubroy, Judy audio recording, transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Judy Dubroy; Textual records; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    - Dubroy, Judy [audio], 1978; F-10-1-0-0-4-1; 1 audio cassette 2 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2894)
      Judy Dubroy; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2894 also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C10-1-0-4, F-10-item50, F-10-1-0-0-0-4.
      - Obj-2894_side1.wav
      - Obj-2894_side2.wav
  - Employment and Immigration Canada, 1978 - 1979; F-10-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Textual records
  - Fraser Lake audio recordings, transcripts and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Marquis, Dean [audio], 28 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-6-1; 1 audio cassette 2 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2909)
      Dean Marquis; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2909 also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-10.1, F-10-item4, F-10-1-0-0-0-10.
      - OBJ_2909SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2909SideB.wav
    - Wolfson, Elaine [audio], 30 September 1978 - 1 October 1978; F-10-1-0-0-6-2; 6 audio cassettes 5 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2936, Audio cassette OBJ-2937, Audio cassette OBJ-2938, Audio cassette OBJ-3023, Audio cassette OBJ-3024, Audio cassette OBJ-3025)
      Elaine Wolfson; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      .wav files also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-23.1, C-10-1-0-23.2, C-10-1-0-23.3, F-10-item43, F-10-item44, F-10-item45, F-10-1-0-0-0-23.
      - OBJ-2936_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2936_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2937_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2937_prt2_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2938_prt3_sideA.wav
    - McLean, Betty, 30 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-6-3; 1 audio cassette 2 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2910)
      McLean, Betty; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      .wav file also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-11.1, F-10-item5, F-10-1-0-0-0-11.
      - OBJ_2910SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2910SideB.wav
  - Harvey, Joanne audio recording, transcript and notes, [ca 1978]; F-10-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Harvey, Joanne; Textual records
    - Harvey, Joanne [audio], 5 October 1978; F-10-1-0-0-7-1; 4 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2904, Audio cassette OBJ-2905, Audio cassette OBJ-3009, Audio cassette OBJ-3010)
      Harvey, Joanne; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-8.1, C-10-1-0-8.2, F-10-item64, F-10-item65, F-10-1-0-0-0-8.
      - OBJ-2904SideA.wav
      - OBJ-2904SideB.wav
      - OBJ-2905SideA.wav
      - OBJ-2905SideB.wav
  - Kitimat audio recordings, transcripts and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Textual records; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    - Fraser, Mary Jane [audio], 21 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-8-1; 5 audio cassettes 6 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2895, Audio cassette OBJ-2896, Audio cassette OBJ-2897, Audio cassette OBJ-2898, Audio cassette OBJ-3005)
      Mary Jane Fraser; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2895 and OBJ-2898: Side B is blank.
      OBJ-2895, OBJ-2896, OBJ-2897 and OBJ-2898 are also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-5.1, C-10-1-0-5.2, C-10-1-0-5.3, C-10-1-0-5.4, F-10-item51, F-10-item52, F-10-item53, F-10-item54, F-10-1-0-0-0-5.
      - Obj-2895_sideA.wav
      - Obj-2896_sideA.wav
      - Obj-2896_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2897_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-2897_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-2898_SideA.wav
    - Gordichuk, Gwyn [audio], 23 September 1978 - 26 September 1878; F-10-1-0-0-8-2; 5 audio cassettes 7 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2899, Audio cassette OBJ-2900, Audio cassette OBJ-2901, Audio cassette OBJ-3006, Audio cassette OBJ-3007)
      Gwyn Gordichuck; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2901 Side B is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-6.1, C-10-1-0-6.2, C-10-1-0-6.3, F-10-item56, F-10-item57, F-10-item58, F-10-1-0-0-0-6.
      - OBJ_2899_SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2899_SideB.wav
      - OBJ_2900_SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2900_SideB.wav
      - OBJ_2901_SideA.wav
      - OBJ_3006SideA.wav
      - OBJ_3006SideB.wav
    - Gutherie, Carol [audio], 25 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-8-3; 3 audio cassettes 3 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2902, Audio cassette OBJ-2903, Audio cassette OBJ-3008)
      Gutherie, Carol; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2903: Side B is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-7.1, C-10-1-0-7.2, F-10-item62, F-10-item61, F-10-1-0-0-0-7.
      - OBJ_2902SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2902SideB.wav
      - OBJ_2903_SideA.wav
    - Nixon, Chris [audio], 24 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-8-4; 3 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2919, Audio cassette OBJ-2920, Audio cassette OBJ-3015)
      Nixon, Chris; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-15.1, C-10-1-0-15.2, F-10-item16, F-10-item17, F-10-1-0-0-0-7.
      - OBJ-2919_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2919_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2920_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2920_prt2_sideB.wav
    - Sorley, Iris [audio], 25 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-8-5; 4 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2926, Audio cassette OBJ-2927, Audio cassette OBJ-3016, Audio cassette OBJ-3017)
      Iris Sorley; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-18.1, C-10-1-0-18.2, F-10-item26, F-10-item27, F-10-1-0-0-0-18.
      - OBJ-2926_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2926_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2927_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2927_prt2_sideB.wav
  - Levitz, Rita transcript and notes, [ca 1978]; F-10-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Levitz, Rita; Textual records
  - Macpherson, Alice audio recording and transcript, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Macpherson, Alice; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Macpherson, Alice [audio], 1978; F-10-1-0-0-10-1; 5 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2906, Audio cassette OBJ-2907, Audio cassette OBJ-2908, Audio cassette OBJ-3011, Audio cassette OBJ-3012)
      Macpherson, Alice; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-9.1, C-10-1-0-9.2, C-10-1-0-9.3, F-10-item68, F-10-item69, F-10-item70, F-10-1-0-0-0-9.
      - OBJ_3011SideA.wav
      - OBJ_3011SideB.wav
      - OBJ_3012SideA.wav
      - OBJ_3012SideB.wav
  - Mercer, Pat and Charlotte Croquette audio recording, transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Mercer, Pat; Croquette, Charlotte; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Mercer, Pat [audio], 6 October 1978; F-10-1-0-0-11-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-2911, Audio cassette OBJ-2912)
      Mercer, Pat; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-12.1, C-10-1-0-12.2, F-10-item6, F-10-item7, F-10-1-0-0-0-12.
      - OBJ_2911SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2911SideB.wav
      - OBJ_2912SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2912SideB.wav
  - Moore, Helen audio recordings and transcript, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Moore, Helen; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Moore, Helen [audio], 11 September 1978 - 12 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-12-1; 5 audio cassettes 3 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2913, Audio cassette OBJ-2914, Audio cassette OBJ-2915, Audio cassette OBJ-3013, Audio cassette OBJ-3014)
      Moore, Helen; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      .wav files also available in mp4 format
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-13.1, C-10-1-0-13.2, C-10-1-0-13.3, F-10-item8, F-10-item9, F-10-item10, F-10-1-0-0-0-13.
      - OBJ_2913SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2913SideB.wav
      - OBJ_2914SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2914SideB.wav
      - OBJ_2915SideA.wav
      - OBJ_2915SideB.wav
  - Murphy, Shannon audio recordings and transcript, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Murphy, Shannon; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Murphy, Shannon [audio], 1 October 1978; F-10-1-0-0-13-1; 3 audio cassettes 3 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2916, Audio cassette OBJ-2917, Audio cassette OBJ-2918)
      Murphy, Shannon; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2916 is blank; OBJ-2918 Side B is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-14.1, C-10-1-0-14.2, C-10-1-0-14.3, F-10-item13, F-10-item14, F-10-item15, F-10-1-0-0-0-14.
      - OBJ-2917_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2917_prt2_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2918_prt3_sideA.wav
  - Omer, Pat audio recordings, transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Omer, Pat; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Omer, Pat [audio], 1978; F-10-1-0-0-14-1; 2 audio cassettes 1 .wav file (Audio cassette OBJ-2921, Audio cassette OBJ-2922)
      Omer, Pat; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2921 Side B is inaudible. OBJ-2922 is blank.
      .wav file also available in .mp4 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-16.1, C-10-1-0-16.2, F-10-item19, F-10-item20, F-10-1-0-0-0-16.
      - OBJ-2921_prt1_sideA.wav
  - Parent, Sue audio recordings, transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 10-1)
    Parent, Sue; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Parent, Sue, 8 September 1978 - 9 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-15-1; 3 audio cassettes 6 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2923, Audio cassette OBJ-2924, Audio cassette OBJ-2925)
      Parent, Sue; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      .wav files also available in .mp3 format
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-17.1, C-10-1-0-17.2, C-10-1-0-17.3, F-10-item21, F-10-item22, F-10-item23, F-10-1-0-0-0-17.
      - OBJ-2923_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2923_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2924_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2924_prt2_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2925_prt3_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2925_prt3_sideB.wav
  - Prince George transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
  - Prince Rupert transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
  - Queen Charlotte Islands audio recordings, transcript and notes, [ca 1978]; F-10-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
    - Sylvie [audio], 3 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-18-1; 2 audio cassettes 3 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2931, Audio cassette OBJ-2932)
      Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-2932 Side B is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-21.1, C-10-1-0-21.2, F-10-item35, F-10-item36, F-10-1-0-0-0-21.
      - OBJ-2931_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2931_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2932_prt2_sideA.wav
  - Sowden, Linda audio recordings, transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
    Sowden, Linda; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Sowden, Linda, 6 September 1978 - 7 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-19-1; 4 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2928, Audio cassette OBJ-2929, Audio cassette OBJ-3018, Audio cassette OBJ-3019)
      Sowden, Linda; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-19.1, C-10-1-0-19.2, F-10-item28, F-10-item29, F-10-1-0-0-0-19.
      - OBJ-2928_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2928_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2929_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2929_prt2_sideB.wav
  - Stanley, Anne audio recording and profile, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
    Stanley, Anne; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Stanley, Anne [audio], 1978; F-10-1-0-0-20-1; 1 audio cassette 2 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2930)
      Stanley, Anne; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-20, F-10-item34, F-10-1-0-0-0-20.
      - OBJ-2930_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2930_sideB.wav
  - Statistics and notes, 1979; F-10-1-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
  - Thompson, Louise audio recordings, transcript and notes, 1978; F-10-1-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
    Thompson, Louise; Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Thompson, Louise [audio], 6 September 1978 - 12 September 1978; F-10-1-0-0-22-1; 6 audio cassettes 5 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2933, Audio cassette OBJ-2934, Audio cassette OBJ-2935, Audio cassette OBJ-3020, Audio cassette OBJ-3021, Audio cassette OBJ-3022)
      Thompson, Louise; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      .wav files also available in .mp4 format
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-1-0-22.1, C-10-1-0-22.2, C-10-1-0-22.3, F-10-item37, F-10-item38, F-10-item39, F-10-1-0-0-0-22.
      - OBJ-2933_prt1_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2933_prt1_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2934_prt2_sideA.wav
      - OBJ-2934_prt2_sideB.wav
      - OBJ-2935_prt3_sideA.wav
  - Waddell, Chris transcript, notes, reference material, 1979; F-10-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 10-2)
    Waddell, Chris; Textual records
- Europe interviews, 1984; F-10-2; 3 sound recordings 9 .wav files; Physical description: series contains 3 sound recordings stored on 4 audio cassettes (originals). Audio cassettes have been digitized to .wav format.
  In 1983 the Vancouver Women in Trades Association raised money to send Kate Braid to Groningen, Holland, for an international workshop on women in non-traditional work. She traveled further to Denmark and England, and conducted interviews with tradeswomen, including Judy Secker. Series consists of audio cassettes of the interviews.
  Records in electronic form (digitized)
  - Secker, Judy (England), 1984; F-10-2-0-0-0-1; 1 audio cassette 2 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2939)
    Secker, Judy; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-2-0-1, F-10-item73.
    - OBJ-2939_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-2939_sideB.wav
  - Non-traditional occupations congress, Denmark, 1984; F-10-2-0-0-0-2; 2 audio cassettes 4 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-2940, Audio cassette OBJ-2941)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-10-2-0-2, C-10-2-0-3, F-10-item74, F-10-item75.
    - OBJ-2940_prt1_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-2940_prt1_sideB.wav